剧情回顾...
Previously on LOST
那是架直升机吗?
Is that a helicopter?
直升机该是这个声音吗?
Is that how a helicopter supposed to sound?
离她远点!
Get away from her!
Desmond
怎么了?
What's wrong?
-我已经结婚了   -是啊
- What's wrong is I'm married.  - Right.
恐怕是个坏消息
I'm afraid... the new is not good.
你们怀孕的可能性...
The chances of conceiving are...
几乎为零
impossible.
你怀孕了
you're pregnant.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
早上好Jack
Good morning,jack.
需要帮助吗?
You need a hand?
谢谢
Thank you.
早些时候我来过你的帐篷
I came by your tent earlier.
Jin走了吗?
Is jin gone?
他和Charlie  Hurley还有Desmond一起走了
He went off with charlie,hurley and desmond.
你要找他吗?
Did you need him?
其实我是来找你的
Actually,I was looking for you.
我想知道你现在怀孕的情况
I wanted to see how you were doing with your pregnancy.
一切都很好
I'm doing fine.
-只是有些累  但这很正常是吗?   -当然
- A little tired,but that's normal,right?  - Sure.
-还有晨吐吗?  -已经没有了
- Any morning sickness? - Not anymore.
出过血吗?
Any bleeding?
为什么你要问我这些问题Jack?
Why are you asking me all these questions,jack?
我只是例行检查一下
I'm just checking in.
现在我回到了这里...
I mean,now that I'm back,I just...
想确保你一切都好
wanted to make sure that you were doing okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
我很好
I'm okay.
行
Great.
翻译：   许愿   后期：梁良
■
你好
Hello
Kwon夫人?
Mrs.Kwon?
Jin
我还是不习惯别人叫我"Kwon夫人"
I'm still not used to "Mrs.Kwon."
我们已经结婚了,你就习惯起来吧
Well get used to it.you're a married woman now.
猜怎么着?  我找到了一些很漂亮的日用织品
Guess what? I found amazing linens for the apartment.
你喜欢的就是我喜欢的
If you like them,I love them.
现在是午饭时间,我正巧在家里
I'm home right now. I stopped by on my lunch hour.
看起来怎么样?
How does it look?
都是些盒子
Lots of boxes.
不过我把床都准备好了
But I got the bed set up.
知道你会这样
Why doesn't that surprise me?
我要回公司了
I have to get back to the office.
晚上见
See you tonight.
Kwon先生?
Mr.Kwon?
是的Kwon夫人?
Yes,Mrs.Kwon?
我非常爱你
I love you madly.
我也很爱你
I love you too.
这上面的人是你吗?
Is this you?
是啊
Yes,it is.
恭喜你了
Congratulations.
他真的很英俊
He's very handsome.
我是个幸运的女孩
I'm a lucky girl.
真的很幸运
Very lucky.
你父亲是Paik先生? 汽车集团的那个?
Your father is Mr.Paik? Of Paik Automotive?Paik
很有权势的家族
Very powerful family.
我和家族生意真的没多大关系
I don't really have much to do with the family business.
那你岳父母呢?
What about your husband's parents?
他的父母都去世了
His parents are dead.
是吗...?
Really...?
你是谁?
Who are you?
如果被大众知道...
It would bring much shame if it was known...
Paik先生的女儿...
...that Mr.Paik's daughter...
嫁给一个渔夫的儿子,那会带来很多羞辱的
...married the son of a fisherman.
这没什么大不了的
I know that and it doesn't matter.
真的吗?
Really?
那你知不知道他也是一个妓女的儿子?
Did you know he was also the son of a prostitute?
你怎么敢!
How dare you!
3天后我会回到这里来
I will be back here in three days.
下午5点
At five P.M.
你要给我10万美元
You will bring me one hundred thousand dollars.
如果你真的爱你丈夫的话...
If you love your husband as "madly" as you say...
就别让他知道这耻辱的事实
...you will spare him the shame of learning the truth.
-她是谁?  -我也不知道
- who is she?  - I have no idea
看上去她认识你  伙计  她刚叫了你的名字
She seems to know you,dude.She just said your name.
我从没见过她
I've never seen her before in my life.
她就要醒了
she's waking up.
她正试着说话.我们给她弄点水
she's trying to talk.We should get her some water.
-帮我一把   -没问题
- Hey,give me a hand.  - Yeah.
-(西班牙语...)   -她在说什么?
- me estoy muriendo.  - What's she saying?
我不知道
I don't know.
西班牙语  伙计
Spanish,dude.
什么  那你能听懂咯?
What,do you understand her,then?
(西班牙语...)
Estoy muriendo.
-她说她快不行了-(西班牙语...)
- She says she's dying.- Me estoy muriendo.
(西班牙语...)
Estoy...
-我的天哪!  - 是根树枝!
- oh,my god! - Oh,it's a branch!
一定是落下来的时候,不小心撞到的
She must have hit it on the way down.
把她的背包拿来,急救箱里的东西快用完了
Uh,get her pack.We haven't got much in this first aid kit.
-看看那里面有什么可以利用的   -如果这是次救援呢?
- See if there's anything we can use in there.- What if this is a rescue?
如果是她找到了我们?  如果...
What if she came for us?  W--
她会没事的,我们不能让她...
I mean,is she gonna be okay? We can't let her--
快去找啊!
well,just go and start looking!
Jack
we go.Jack.
Jack...我们得尽快把她带到Jack那去
jack--we have to get her to jack as soon as possible.
-她也许是我们离开这座岛的唯一希望  -我们不能动她  那会更糟
- She could be our way off the island.- No,if we move her,it'll make it worse.
我们就眼看着她流血致死吗?
Oh,we just let her bleed to death?
不  我们得把Jack找来
No,we-- we need to bring jack here.
从那里走来单程也要8小时!
It's an 8-hour walk one way!
那我跑去
Then I'll run.
你疯了吗? 这很危险
You're out of your mind.It's not safe.
天黑了  鬼知道丛林里有什么? 不要忘了...
It's gonna be dark soon.Who knows who's out in this jungle? In case you have forgotten,
这岛上还有人才辈出想杀了我们
there are people on this island trying to kill us.
没人知道我们在这里!
Nobody knows we're here!
不好意思
oops.
惊喜!
Surprise!
我买了你最爱喝的豆腐汤
I got your favorite--tofu soup.
谢谢  但我先得处理这些盒子
Thank you.Let me finish this box.
一会儿再弄吧,先吃点东西
We'll unpack later.Let's eat.
你介意我把这个放在桌子上吗?
Do you mind if I put this on the table?
当然不
Not at all.
就算穿了这身衣服...
Even in a cap and gown...
你还是我见过最性感的女人
...you're the sexiest woman I've ever seen.
你没有自己家人的照片吗?
Don't you have and pictures of your family?
我长大的时候...
We didn't have a ...
连台相机都没有
...camera growing up.
一张都没有吗?
No pictures at all?
那...
Well...
你父亲就没留给你些吗?
...didn't your father leave you any?
没有  我参军时父亲就去世了
No, I was in the army when he died.
参军?  你说你父亲去世时你才16岁
The army? You said your father died when you were sixteen.
不  是在我参军时
No.I was in the army.
但你告诉我...
But you told me --
你一定是弄错了
You must've misunderstood.
你问这个干嘛Sun?
What is this about,Sun?
这...
It's...
没什么  我很抱歉
It's nothing. I'm sorry.
汤快凉了
Your soup is getting cold.
这样好吗?
how's this?
这样不错
That's perfect.
谢谢
Thank you.
Jack和"the others"在一起的时候发生了什么?
What do you think happened to jack while he was with the others?
他好像有点变了
Since he's been back,he seems different.
他说他也就是个囚犯
He says that he was pretty much a prisoner,and
他和他们合作的唯一原因就是他认为他们能让他离开这里
the only reason why he cooperated is 'cause he thought they'd let him off the island.
你真的相信他吗?
Do you believe him?
为什么不呢?
Why wouldn't I?
他问我怀孕的事
He came to me,asking about my pregnancy.
那这也不能和...
Well,what would that have anything to do--
如果...
what if...
"the others"想要我的孩子呢?
what if the others want my baby?
他在那儿已经一个星期了
He's beethere alone for over a week.
也许他在为他们做事
How do we know he isn't working with them?
他才不会这么做
He's not working with them.
你知道些什么吗Kate?
Do you know something,kate?
是Juliet
It's juliet.
她是他们的医生...他们的...
She was their doctor-- their--
妇产科医生  专门研究这里的孕妇...
their fertility doctor,studyi pregnant women,and
当Claire病的时候 她告诉我和Jack...
when claire was sick,she told me and jack...
"the others"要孩子的原因...
the reason the others wanted her baby...
是为了做研究
was for research.
Sun!
-等等  你不必这么做的  -这与你无关Kate
- Wait.You don't have to do this.- Go away,kate.
我想了解一下你的研究
I want to know about your research.
Sun...
孕妇会怎么样?
what happens to pregnant women?
你怀孕了?
You're pregnant.
你肯定吗?你是怎么知道的?
Are you sure? How do you know?
我问你问题呢!
I asked you a question.
大家不在乎你在这里洗衣服吃东西
Everyone else might be all right with you washing your clothes and eating our food,
但我想知道到底发生了什么?
but I want to know what's going on.
我要答案
I want answers.
你们那些人在干什么? 为什么要带走孩子?
What are you people doing? Why are you taking children?
孕妇在这座岛上会怎么样?
What happens to pregnant women on this island?
-到底会...  -他们会死
- What happens--  - they die.
他们都会死
They all die.
Sun我们走吧
sun,come on.Let's go.
她在说什么?
what is she saying?
汉语...不是韩语
Chinese...  not korean.
也许我们该把它拔出来
Maybe we should just pull it out.
-那会更糟.-你忘了这里有多危险吗?
Noyou'll just make it worse.- Have you forgotten what's at stake here?
难道这又是你的预感? 这次是谁的脖子中箭了?
Or is this just another one of your flashes? Who's getting an arrow in the neck this time?
难道你忘了吗 她叫了我的名字!
lest you forget,she said my bloody name!
她还有我和女友的照片
She had a photo of me and my girlfriend.
我知道什么? 我知道的比你们多的多!
Do I understand? I understand better than the lot of you!
伙计们  冷静一点
Hey,guys,chill.
我们已经浪费了很多时间
We've wasted enough time already.
你不能离开这里
Hey,you're not leaving us.
-请让开Charlie   -不!
- Just get out of my way,charlie.- No!
Jin!
-Jin!
你是谁?
who are you?
我问你,你是谁?
I said,who are you?
就是他射伤了Sayid
He's the guy who shot sayid.
Kate告诉我们的,Locke把他住的那个站给炸飞了
Kate told us.He lived out in that station that locke blew up.
他是他们的人
He's an other.
我以为Locke已经用电磁防御系统杀了他了
I thought locke killed that guy with the electro-fence thingy.
你只有5秒钟,否则我就开枪了
You've got five seconds to talk,or I fire this gun,brother.
-这是信号枪-你应该知道...
- That's a flare gun.- And how do you think it'll feel...
在这个距离被信号枪射中心脏的滋味吧?
taking a flare to the chest at this range?
你朋友已经说过了,我这周已经死过一次了
As your friend pointed out,I already died once this week.
(意大利语...)
你能听懂她
You understand her.
她说的是意大利语
She's speaking italian.
她说她快不行了.她需要帮助
She said she's dying. She needs help.
我曾是苏联军队里的军医.我能帮助你们
I was a soviet army field medic.I can offer you my services.
-等等  你在干嘛?  -救她的命
- Wait.What are you doing?- I'm saving her.
树枝刺穿了她的肺
This branch has punctured her lung.
里面进了血
It's filling with blood.
如果不能吸入空气,她会死的
If it is not ventilated soon,she's going to die.
好吧  你干吧  帮帮她
Well,do it. Help her.
如果我救了她.你们得让我走
If I fix her,you must let me walk away as if I never came upon you.
你还需要什么?
What do you need?
不好意思  你是Kwon先生吗?
Excuse me. Are you Mr.Kwon?
是啊
Yes.
你一定是Sun
You must be Sun.
谢谢
Thank you.
和我说说你们的婚礼
Please.Tell me about your wedding.
那很美
It was beautiful.
那是我生命中最快乐的一天
The happiest day of my life.
我想我儿子也是
And my son's,too,I imagine.
Kwon先生
Mr.Kwon.
你怎么没有参加婚礼?
Why weren't you at the wedding?
他告诉你什么了?
What did he tell you?
他告诉我...
He told me...
你已经去世了
You were dead.
他为什么要这么说?
Why would he say that?
为了不让大家知道他家庭的耻辱
To avoid the shame of where he came from.
这就是你为什么要告诉他...
And is that why you told him...
他母亲在他还是婴儿时就去世了?
...his mother died when he was a baby?
他的母亲...
His mother...
和很多男人好过
She was with many men.
她把孩子留给了我
She left me with the baby.
我独自把他抚养大
I raised him alone.
我甚至都不确定他是我的孩子
I wasn't even sure I was the father.
但还有谁会肯照顾他呢?
But who else would take care of him?
你很美
You are so beautiful.
和荣幸见到你
It pleases me so much to meet you.
不要和他说你来见过我...
You can never tell him that you met me...
还有他母亲还活着
...or that this mother is still alive.
求你了...
Please...
就为了我
...for me.
别...
Do not...
别让他为了这耻辱而受苦
Do not make him suffer this shame.
别出声
be quiet.
别动
你想我帮你和你的孩子吗?
You want me to help you and your baby?
我已经回答过你了,现在你必须跟我来
I have answers to your questions,but you ha to come with me right now.
就你和我
Just you and me,nobody else.
如果你说的是实话,那我早就死了
if what you said was true,that means I'm already dead.
我干嘛还要跟你去?
Why should I go anywhere with you?
因为你还是有希望的
Because there may be hope for you yet.
我们要去哪儿?
Where are we going?
这附近有个医疗站,那里有超声波仪器
There's a medical station near here.They have an ultrasound machine
Claire和Kate告诉过我那个地方
Claire and kate told me about that place.
那里已经被遗弃了.什么都找不到
It was abandoned.They found nothing there.
那是因为他们不知道要找哪里
Well,that's because they didn't know where to look.
你要对我做什么?
What are you going to do to me?
我要检查你肚子里的孩子D.O.C...
I'm gonna look at your baby and determine the D.O.C.--
怀孕的日期
Um,date of conception.
超声波仪器会告诉我们你是几时怀孕的  误差在1天内
The ultrasound will tell me when you got pregnant,give or take a day.
如果你是在岛外怀孕的,那你和你的孩子就会没事的
If you got pregnant off the island,then you and your baby will probably be okay,
但如果你是在这里怀孕的...
but if you got pregnant here...
到时候再想办法吧
we'll cross that bridge when we come to it.
你和你丈夫最近一次做爱是什么时候?
When was the last time you and your husband had sex?
我情愿不回答你的问题
I would rather not talk about that.
我知道这是隐私  但如果我知道是什么时候  我可以...
Look,I know that it's personal,but if I know when,then I can figure--
那个机器不是能告诉我们吗?
isn't that what the machine will do?
当然
Yeah.
那我们继续走吧
Then let's keep walking.
Paik先生
Mr.Paik.
你女儿想要见你
Your daughter is here to see you.
新婚快乐
Congratulations on your wedding.
谢谢
Thank you.
祝你们幸福
We wish you much happiness.
你怎么来了?
To what do I owe this visit?
我想让你帮个忙
I need to ask you a favor.
怎么了  亲爱的?
What is it,my dear?
我...我需要...
I... I need...
10万美元
One hundred thousand dollars.
为了什么?
What for?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
你不给我一个解释,我怎么能给你钱?
Why should I give you money without an explanation?
因为我一生...
Because my whole life...
都假装不知道你在做什么
...I've pretended not to know what you do.
一直好好的听从你
I've allowed you to keep your control over me.
我假装一切都很好
I pretend that everything is all right.
我会继续这样装下去
I will continue pretending.
只要你给我这笔钱
As long as you give me the money I am asking for.
别问我理由
No questions asked.
这世界上人人都有发问的权力!
We do not live in a world where there are no questions asked!
我这么做是为了让我深爱的人远离耻辱
I'm doing this to spare someone I love deep shame.
你的丈夫?
Your new husband?
如果这钱是为了你的丈夫...
If the money is for your husband...
那就该他来还这笔债
It is he who will bear this debt.
他不再是部门经理了
He will no longer be a floor manager.
他将为我工作
He will be working for me.
你们对这个女人还了解多少?
what else do you know about this woman?
除了信号枪她还有什么?
Did she have anything on her besides the flare gun?
一本书  还有个无线电,电话什么的...
Just a book,a fancy radio/phone thingy...
它好使吗?
does it work?
好使的话我早告诉你了
Like I'd tell you.
需要一个人帮忙
One of you must help.
其他人给我留出空间
The rest,clear the way.I need space.
我来做
I'll do it.
尽可能的帮她擦血
Wipe away as much of the blood as you can.
需要把空气排出来!
need to evacuate the air now!
把她按住了
Hold her steady.
稳住!
Steady!
我知道了
Yeah,I-I heard you.
这样...正常吗?
is that... normal?
纱布
gauze.
小心的包扎起来
Tape it. Be careful.
不要太紧了
The covering needs to be hollow.
伤口需要透气
The wound needs to breathe.
她说了什么?
what did she say?
"谢谢"
"Thank you."
她说"谢谢你们救了我"
She said,"thank you for helping me."
就在这下面
It's right down here.
你为什么要这么做?
why are you doing this?
什么?
What?
帮助我
Helping me.
从前...
Once upon a time,
我告诉别人他们怀孕时
I told women that they were pregnant,
他们的表情告诉我...
and their faces...
这是他们一生中听到最好的消息
it was the best news they ever got in their entire life.
然而我到了这里
Then I came here.
在过去的3年里...
in the last three years.
我们失去了9位病人
I've lost...nine patients...
我帮助你是因为我想告诉你...
I'm helping you because I want to tell you
你是在来这之前怀孕的
that you and your husband got pregnant before you came here.
我帮助你是因为我想告诉你好的消息
I'm helping you because I want to give good news again.
我和其他男人上床了...
I slept with another man...
在来这里之前
Before we got to the island.
Jin和我...
Jin and I,we were having...
遇到了些麻烦,我们没有...
trouble.We weren'T...
我有一个朋友
and I had a friend.
那是个错误
It was a mistake.
我们都会犯错
We all make mistakes.
哪边走?
Which way?
能帮我挪一下吗?
will you help me move this forward?
好了
good.
为什么这个房间被隐藏起来了?
why is this room hidden?
别担心
Don't worry about it.
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
告诉我
Tell me.
我们把要死的女人都带来这里
It's where we brought the women to die.
她没事
She's fine.
尽量保持伤口的清洁
Keep the wound as clean as you can.
一天后她会好起来的
She should be better in a day.
一天?
A day?
她的肺被刺穿了
Her lung was punctured.
这座岛上的  自然规律有些不同
On this island,the rules are a bit different.
也许一天半
Maybe a day and a half.
我做了该做的
I did as I promised.
她会活下来的
She will live.
-你不会真的放他走吧    -你走吧
- You can't seriously be considering letting him go. - Just go.
开什么玩笑?.他是他们的人!
Are you kidding?He's one of them!
我又能怎么做Charlie?
So what would you have me do,charlie?
我们得做个担架来抬她走
We've t to make a stretcher and carry her.
你想让我再带上个囚犯吗?
How are we gonna do that and bring a prisoner?
-给我根绳子  -责任由我来负
- Give me some rope. - I'll take responsibility.
电话  电话!
Phone. Phone!
-Jin等等!  -电话!
- Wait,jin! - Phone!
-没关系的Jin!
-不  让他去吧!
-快回来Jin!    -让他去追吧!
- Jin,come back here! - Oi,let him!
-没关系的Jin! Jin! -电话!
- Jin,it's all right! -  no,let him!
Jin让他走吧
Jin,let him go!
Jin让他走吧!
电话!
Phone!
是你偷走的?
You stole this?
不试试怎么知道?
How could you respect me if I didn't try?
要不要弄瞎你另一只眼睛?
How about I take your other eye?
你会试试吗?
Would you respect that?
抱歉  我...
Sorry. I--
住手Charlie!
charlie,don't!
Charlie!
Charlie让他走吧!
Charlie,let him go!
这是一个错误!
This is a mistake!
我们不能就这么放了他!
We can't keep letting these people go!
我保证过他!
We gave him our word!
走吧
Go on.
滚远点
Get out of here.
这不是Jin的孩子
the baby isn't jin'S.
我们在韩国试着生孩子,但我们不能
We tried to have a baby back in korea and couldn'T.
医生告诉我...
And the doctor...
Jin他不能生育
he told me jin was infertile.
然后你来了这里
And then you came here.
什么?
What?
你知道男人精子的平均数量是...
Did you know that the average male sperm count is
6到8千万?
between 60 and 80 million?
不过在这座岛上是那的5倍之多
But on this island,it's five times that.
这样的几率很高
We call that good odds.
准备好了吗?
you ready?
是的
Yes.
把你的上衣撩起来一点
Okay,you wanna lift up your shirt a little?
会有些凉
It's cold.
我能看见我的孩子吗?
will I see the baby?
也许吧
Maybe.
你只有3个月,所以还不能确定
It's your first trimester,so it's a little iffy.
如果你看不见心跳
if you don't see a heartbeat,
别担心  因为现在还早
don't worry about it.It's just early.
这是怎么工作的?
How does it work?
我测量一下胎儿
Well,I take a measurement
这就能告诉我
of the fetus,and that will tell us
你是什么时候受孕的
when your baby was conceived
我们就可以知道是谁的孩子了
and then we'll know who.
你还好吗?
are you okay?
我得到的都会是坏消息
I lose either way.
如果我能活下来...
If I'm going to live...
那就意味着这不是Jin的孩子
that means the baby's not jin'S.
你还想继续吗?
Do you still want to do this?
-是的-好吧
- Yes.- Okay.
真相的时刻
Moment of truth.
Kwon夫人
Mrs.Kwon
Kwon先生
Mr.Kwon
我听说你今天来过办公室
I heard you came by the office today.
怎么不来打个招呼?
Why didn't you come say hello?
我不想打扰你
I didn't want to bother you.
能见到你,永远都不会
Seeing you is never a bother.
下一次  我一定会来
Next time,i promise.
你去拿过信了吗?
Did you get the mail?
抱歉  我给忘了
Sorry,i forgot.
信箱钥匙在你那儿吗?
Do you have the mail key?
在我包里
It's in my purse.
Jin等等!
Jin!Wait!
这些钱是干什么的?
What's this money?
是...我父亲的
It's...from my father.
为什么?
Why?
我想为我们买些家具....
I wanted to get us furniture....
然后渡过一个美好的蜜月
And I wanted us to have a nice honeymoon.
这些我都能给你
I can provide for you.
渡蜜月...家具,我知道还要些时间...
The honeymoon..the furniture.I know it will take longer...
但我会做到的,我能付得起的
but it will happen.And i will pay for it.
我会一直照顾你的Sun
I will always take care of you,Sun.
我知道
I know.
把这些还回去吧
Then give it back.
我欠你父亲够多的了
I don't want to be in your father's debt any more than we already are.
拜托了
Please.
Jin...
我爱你
I love you.
-真的吗?  -真的
- Madly?- Madly?
在这里
there it is.
那是你的孩子,你看见了吗?
There's your baby.Can you see?
我看见了
I can see it.
是男孩还是女孩?
is it a boy or a girl?
这还为时过早
Oh,it's--it's a little early,
你看到这轻微的振动了吗?
but,um,do you see that little flutter?
那是心跳
that's the heart beating.
很强烈的心跳,胎儿很健康
it's very strong.It's very healthy.
好了
Okay.
你们的飞机是90天前坠毁的
you crashed here 90 days ago.
孩子大概是在8周前受孕的
The baby was conceived about eight weeks ago,
所以...是53天左右
so... around 53 days.
你是在这座岛上受孕的
you got pregnant on the island.
我很抱歉  我很抱歉Sun
I am sorry.I'm so sorry,sun.
我会尽力帮助你的
I will do everything that I can.
孩子是Jin的
it's jin'S.
还以为你不会来了
I was starting to think you wouldn't come.
你为什么不告诉我你是Jin的母亲?
Why didn't you tell me you were Jin's mother?
我把他生了下来,那也不能说我就是他的母亲
I gave birth to him.But hat doest not make me his mother.
你知道我们家族的权势有多大
You know how powerful my family is.
我丈夫以为你已经死了
My husband believes that you are dead.
别逼我让这真的发生
Do not force me to make that reality.
我还剩多少时间?
so how long do I have?
大多数孕妇都是在她们的第二个阶段(6个月)
Most of the women made it into the middle of their second trimester.
没人能撑过第三阶段(9个月)
Nobody made it to their third.
那就是2个月
That gives me two months.
我...很高兴孩子是Jin的
I am...very happy the baby's jin'S.
你给我的是好消息Juliet
You gave me good news,juliet.
不客气Sun
It was my pleasure,sun.
我回去看看还忘了什么
I'm gonna go back inside and make sure that I didn't miss anything.
我可不想留下任何痕迹
I don't wanna take the chance that we didn't cover our tracks.
你可以在这儿等一会儿吗?
Do you wanna wait out here?
当然
All right.
Juliet?
谢谢你
Thank you.
Ben现在是星期六早晨6点
ben,it's 6:00 A.M.On saturday morning.
Kwon怀孕了
Kwon is pregnant.
她是在这里受孕的,胎儿很健康
The fetus is healthy and was conceived on island with her husband.
他在来这儿之前不能生育
He was sterile before they got here.
我还在收集其他女人的样本
I'm still working on getting samples from the other women.
应该很快能得到Austen的
I should have austen's soon.
有了新情况我会再通报的
I'll report back when I know more.
我恨你
I hate you.
-你不能相信他们  -你说什么?
- You can't trust 'em,you know.- What's that?
"The others"你放跑那个
The others--the one you let go.
明天他会带着他的兄弟回来的
He'll be back tomorrow with five of his mates.
早该杀了他
Should've killed him.
Charlie  绑紧些
Charlie.Uh,tight.
好吧
Oh,okay.
老兄
You know,brother,
算起来
by my count,
你们比他们杀了更多的人
you've killed more of them than they've killed of you.
都是他们先挑起的
They started it.
不能因为他们中的一个人
You know,just 'cause one comes traipsing back
和Jack  Kate一起回来了,就该相信他们
with jack and kate doesn't mean that we can trust them now.
妈妈?
Mom?
我在哪里?
where am I?
放松点  有根树枝扎进了你的...
Take it easy.You just had a giant branch in your--
-我在哪里? -我不知道
- where am I? - I don't know.
你在一座岛上
You're on an island.
你是来救我们的吗?
Are you here to rescue us?
还会有更多人吗?你能修好电话吗?
Are there more of you?Can you make your phone work?
-你是谁?-Hugo Reyes
- Who are you?- Hugo reyes.
我们是大西洋815上的
I crashed here on oceanic flight 815.
有些人幸存了下来  你是来救我们的吗?你是来找我们的吗?
A bunch of us survived.Is that why you're here?Were you looking for us?
815?  815航班?
815?Flight 815?
-悉尼起飞的那架?-没错!
- The one from sydney?  - Yeah!
-这不可能   -是啊    我知道
- No. That's not possible.  - Yeah,I know.
-这不容易  我们要找食物...   -不不
- It wasn't easy,but we found food -   - no,no
-在舱门里  有很多食物...  -不  815航班...他们...
- In the hatch,more food- - no,flight 815--   they...
找到了那架飞机
they found the plane.
没有幸存者
There were no survivors.
他们都死了
They were all dead.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■